(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-30T23:05:20.767160",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
SPECIAL MISSION ASSIGNED.
UNDERCOVER INVESTIGATION
TARGET: FIVE ESCAPED FUGITIVES
TEAM: JUSTICE
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Gigi Murin
Raora Panthera
Cecilia Immergreen
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all be-
Taking you all below, taking you all be-
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
Taking you all below, below we go
They think they want it? (Huh?)
They wanna ge-get down
We take 'em down (down, down)
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck
End up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run or hide and scream out
Already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down
Throwing the keys out, shut down
I~
Love it, the forbidden
You're never forgiven
Not one to just forget
We got 'em
The higher I rise
Down further you dive
Standin' on the...
Standing on the...
...edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you somethin'...
Show you something...
...real, my level, no, you'll never know, as above so...
...below, you should know
We got it!
Run in the light, oh my dio
What's wrong, what's right?
Rushin' in a fantasy
Rushing in a fantasy
Wannabe disease
Sure that you won't ever make it out
Eyes follow now
Do it, do it
New target locked on it now (now)
Oh yeah, oh!
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop, it's just...
...the start! Ooh...
Get down, get da-ra-da
Like it like that, run it like that
Get down, get down, down, down, down, hey
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know
Don't ya (they know it)
Run in the light, oh, my dio
What's wrong, what's right with you?
Run in the night, oh, my dio
Come take a bite
Never ending, endless sky
(Justice) Love it, the forbidden
(Just like that) You're never forgiven
(Justice) Not one to just forget
(Get, get that) We rise
(Wow, yeah, we rise, rise, rise)
Standin' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical, you
Got nowhere to go, show you somethin' real
My level, no, you'll never know, as above so below, you should know
Just a little unpredictable, beautiful
Just the start, let's get it, let's get 'em, baby
Go next level, almost criminal, as above so
It goes below
Yay!
Hello, everyone!
At last, we are in 3D! And we've gotten to perform Above Below!
We're in 3D!
Did you like our performance? Was it awesome?
It was so awesome!
If you really liked the shot from it, remember we have a hashtag #Justice3D! Post it on social media and we'd love to see that!
Yay!
Huzzah! Now that we're finally in 3D, guys, do you want to do an introduction, but full energy with a pose?
Cool poses!
Cool poses? We have...
Cool poses! Right!
Okay.
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order,
the leader of Justice,
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
Lovely to see you, to see you... lovely!
That was so cool!
So cool!
Up next!
Move, everyone! Get away from us!
Hello, everybody! From hololive Justice...
it's Gigi Murin!
On official hololive English channel!
It really is! Haha!
Hi, everyone! It's me, ancient automaton from hololive English -Justice-,
Cecilia Immergreen!
And then, of course, we have our...
Raora!
Ciao, everyone! This is Raora Panthera from hololive English -Justice-!
Big cat means big trouble!
Yay! And everyone, take a look at where we are now!
Ta-da! Whoa, so cool!
Touch the spine!
All right. I guess I gotta take off my skirt.
What? What is she doing? Look away, look away!
Oh my gosh, I can't look at this!
Oh, she's naked. Okay.
It's not naked! These are very, very normal pants, okay?
All right. That felt wrong. That felt wrong.
Well, maybe you shouldn't have done it.
Can you see...
HR? Calling HR!
Liz! Liz!
What's happening now?
They're fighting again. As usual.
Whoa! Stop fighting! Get on your place and shut up!
So guys, what's the plan for today? How about we...
I suggest ice cream! Ice cream!
Well, it's our 3D debut, so I think it'd be nice to do something fun of course, yeah.
Ice cream! Ice cream is fun, right?
We should play a game, maybe a game?
And then whoever wins gets ice cream!
ATTEEEEEEEEEENTION!
Up and at 'em, maggots! It's time to get to work!
No slacking off while I, Sergeant Smokey, am busting my scales off for Justice!
Heeeey, long time no see you! How are you doing?
Hey! Long time no see! How are you doing?
"Heeeey"?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
"Hey"?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
Now line up and stand at attention, peabrains!!
Okay, calm down, dears. Let's just do as Smokey says.
It's his first big appearance, though he seems pretty fired up.
I will do it for you, Liz. All right, let me get over there.
I'll do it for you, Liz. All right, let me get over there.
Enough talking! Do I make myself clear!?
Sir, yes, sir!
I can't hear you!
Show me your war face!
Headquarters tells me you've been getting sloppy, so I'm here to set things straight!
I've got a few brutal challenges lined up to whip your sorry hides into shape!
Woah, look at that! Has that always been there?
Has that always been there? Let's go look!
Has that always been there? Let me go look!
Oh, the frame! Woah!
Alright, read the rules!
Here we are, let's see what it says. 1st Trial: Think Fast, Move Faster!
Rule 1: This is a training exercise for both your brain and your body.
Rule 2: Use the giant keyboard to quickly input the answer to the question shown on the projector.
Rule 3: The trial consists of 10 questions per person. If you're stuck, you can skip and answer it later.
Rule 4: Correct answers with more letters will get higher points.
Rule 5: Let's see who can rack up the most points in 90 seconds!
No whining! Cecilia, you go first! Get in there!
Okay, I'll go first. Get out of my way!
Cecilia, it's up to you! Watch this, guys. Don't worry, I got this.
Are you really ready? How ready are you?
All right, let's get started! You've only got 90 seconds!
3, 2, 1, go!
What is Gigi's last name? M-U-R-I-N! Enter!
One of Raora's goals as an idol is to publish an OOO BOOK!
Elizabeth is from GREAT OOOOOOOO!
E-X-A-R-D-I-A!
Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"? Answer with the full name.
Five points! Five points! W-I-L-L-I-A-M...
S-H-A-K-E-S-P-E-A-R-E!
Enter! A. William Shakespeare!
How many hearts does a fish typically have?
O-N-E! Enter! A. ONE!
Granny Smith and Fuji are types of which fruit? Apple!
Nice try! Okay, that's the only exercise I'm going to do for today!
How many points did I get? Nine points!
That's a pretty good score! A good start!
Next challenger, MOVE IT!! I guess I'll tap in.
Let her show you who's the boss. I'll tap in.
Wait! Oh, they're gonna leave her hanging! You can do it!
All right. I, the leader of Justice, shall go next.
Let's get started. Elizabeth, are you ready?
Yes! Count me in!
Three! Two! One! Go!
All right. One of Raora's nicknames is Big...
You know! You know! You know! C A T. Enter!
Finally, someone who knows my questions.
All right. Cecilia likes to drink... Tea! T E A!
She likes to drink coffee! No, no, tea!
Gigi's fans are called...
Wait, why is that so long? G R E...
Uh-oh.
M... That's a long... Oh, that's a long word! That's so...
L I N G S...
Ah, trick question! It's Gremurins! That's my full name!
Is it really? Yeah, 'cause...
...painted the Mona Lisa! Next question!
What do you call a group of lions?
P...
I don't know. Lions? Speak of lions...
...R I D E. Enter!
Go! Go! Go! Woo! Nice, ER!
Next! Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
Oh, Romans! Romans, I'm fine!
I know this... Oh, I don't think this is...
I T A L Y! I think it was the Roman Empire!
What is that? Does it exist?
What is the fear of confined spaces called?
Next! I don't have enough time anyway. There we go.
No, continuous! Woo!
Of course! Yes! Yes, of course.
Of course I... How do you feel? How do you feel?
Are you tired? What's my score?
What's my score, guys? I think your score's being calculated.
In my brain! In my brain of brains!
I'm carrying the one... It was four! You got four points.
What the freak?!
That was really good.
No Tomates energy's fine.
No, it's because they tricked you with Gremurins!
Cat girl! Let me see your typing paws!
Okay, I go, I go, I go!
You got this, Raora! Yeah!
Let's get started.
Okay. Three! Two! One! Go!
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Don't look at her!
You! You!
Oh, no! It's E!
B L U E. Enter!
Yay! What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
Play again? Oh no. Gigi's mascot?
P O P O.
Yay! Next question.
What is Cecilia's last name?
I M M E... Go, go, go!
E R... She's enunciating it to... Okay!
That's so mean.
QWERTY keyboard!
Wait, Raora... Okay, go, go, go, go, go! Enter!
Yay! Okay. Skip! Too many words! Skip, skip!
How many legs do insects have?
Skip!
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon? Skip! I don't know...
This is a wall clip.
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
Skip, skip, skip, skip! It's too long, she doesn't want to spell that!
What is the highest female vocal range called? You got this one! The 120!
I don't know anything! Good job!
It's okay! I'm sorry.
Gigi, score!
Okay. Calculating, calculating...
Ten, right? Is it 10, right? 20? 20?
It was four.
Why are you sad?
Why are you sad? You tied with me.
Why are you so silent all of a sudden? I got a really good score!
Don't you think Elizabeth did really well? I don't...
I think there is a miscalculation here.
Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
Okay, okay. Next one! Next one!
Okay. Oh, I guess it's me!
What if they ask really hard questions? I'm scared!
You should be scared. I'm scared of really hard questions.
Okay, are you ready, Gigi? I'm ready!
Okay, let's get started. Three, two, one, start!
Which flower best represents Elizabeth? Rose! Skip!
Cecilia's signature greeting is "Spin to..." What? Oh wait, keep it!
W!
I!
N! Enter!
Win!
Y!
T! H!
A!
T! T!
I! N!
I! Enter!
Oh, okay!
I!
S! A!
N! Enter!
Keep it up. Okay, okay, okay.
This feels way shorter than William Shakespeare.
Skip! Skip!
King of fruits.
Only one point!
Skip! Only one point!
What the...
Oh, you got this, you got this!
Big one.
Skip! Skip! I don't care.
I don't care. Skip! I don't care.
Skip, I don't care.
Think about it!
Gigi...
Oh no!
Gigi!
Come on! Come on!
Is it gas or air?
Oxygen!
I think it's gas.
You got this, Gigi!
N! Enter!
No!
Okay, okay, okay...
Isaac Newton versus William Shakespeare...
...and then they give the same amount of points?
That's not...
That's not fair.
Smokey's doing Smokey's.
Yeah, I think it's unfair to play a game where we need to read.
That's not...
Well, anyways, you're the winner!
Do you want to know your score?
What's my score?
Want to know, Gigi?
What is it?
It's 10 points.
You did it!
Good job, Gigi!
This is why you are a member of Justice!
Yes, that's why.
Hmph... Looks like you maggots still need some serious training...
Alright, time for the second trial, you knuckleheads. I got some special training gear for you!
What?
Oh, it's just chilling.
Don't hit me! Don't hit me!
Abuse! What is this?
Ah, yes! We are going to have a duel!
Why is it just me and Liz?
Gigi! Rules!
Rule 1 of Dizzy Combat!
Split into 2 groups!
And then one member on each team is blindfolded.
And we have to spin 5 times!
Spin to win!
Ooh, you're good at this, Gigi!
And after you spin 5 times, you will face off against each other in an epic sword battle!
To the death!
While being blindfolded!
To the death? To the death.
And the teammate that is not blindfolded must guide the other player to hit them.
It's like a co-op game! Co-op game! Okay, okay.
First, before you pick a team, the points for each target:
Head, 5 points.
Each arm, 2 points.
Each knee, 3 points each!
Okay, that makes sense. Got it.
Elizabeth! Gigi! Time for you dirtbags to beat the snot out of each other!
Ah, yes! Huzza! All right, Gigi!
Let's put on our blindfolds!
All right. Blindfolds, blindfolds.
What am I supposed to do? Hey hey hey...
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Okay, you ready?
All right. Okay, I'm ready.
Okay, believe in yourself. Where do I go?
Believe in yourself, I believe in myself.
Okay, no way, I'm going to guide you.
You've got God eye!
Okay, and... and be careful.
I choose you! Gigi-mon!
When do we spin? Do we spin?
You can do it! You are the queen! You are the leader! Grab!
Okay, ready?
Start!
Spin to win!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
Okay, Betha, okay okay okay.
That's it, that's it, okay.
Right in front of you. A little bit... a little bit more.
Well, you have to walk like six steps.
I have the power!
Anime! God and anime on my side!
That's me! Wait, wait, wait!
Don't worry. Wait, wait, left!
Turn to the left! Turn to the left!
Attack, attack, attack! There she is!
There she is! Yes, you got it! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Roll away! Roll away!
Let's go, let's go! She's on the ground! She's on the ground!
She's on the ground!
On your left! On your left! On your left!
Okay, okay, okay.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Turn around!
Got... Got it! There she is! Yeah!
Oh, my hitting!
Oh, my hitting! That's one!
That's two! That's three!
That's really well!
Oh, my hitting! Oh, that's two!
Okay. Okay.
Gigi!
I don't know...
You did it! You did it! You did it!
Well well well, looks like you numbnuts managed to scrape up 15 points in round 1.
15 points! Yeah, 15 points!
15 points!
Yeah, 15, not 50! 15 points!
Alright, alright, gear up for Round 2!
Okay, okay, okay, give us...
The balloon! Balloon!
Isn't your goggles cheating? What? No!
Turn around! Turn around!
All right, let's put your blindfolds on.
Okay, help me, please.
All right. Oh, right. Let's put your blindfold on.
Yes, it's on! Yeah. Okay, now...
Can you see anything? Watch this.
Okay, I'm ready! Let's...
Wait, wait! Hey, hey, hey!
Took you buttercups long enough. Now square up!
All right. Who's over here? Gigi, count us down!
I'm gonna do a countdown!
Three!
Two!
One! And...
One! And two!
Two! Faster! And three!
Three! Faster, faster! And four!
Four! And five!
Okay, left, Raora, left!
Left, left! She's bent over, she's bent over!
Stop! That was a groan!
Turn around the other way! Yeah, behind!
Follow my voice!
Where did she go? Don't follow me!
Raora, straight ahead! Straight ahead!
Straight! Keep going straight!
Get her! Straight! Get her!
No! Go low! Go low!
Go low! Watch out!
She's left again!
Forward, forward! Stay where you are!
Okay, now! Now, now, now, now!
Oh gosh! She's left again!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Forward! Straight! Straight!
In front of me!
Raora, forward! Go!
Raora, straight ahead!
Oh! Oh, my gosh!
That was... That was something.
Gigi, score!
15 points!
That was very... I'm dizzy. I'm dizzy.
I am... I am scared of the darkness.
It is okay, you're still my pretty kitty.
Your third trial is behind that door. What's the password?!
Oh, really? All together!
It's 8-0-0-8!
Open!
Fancy! What are you doing?
Whoa! That's so cool!
How cool! Yes!
Let's go, everyone! Huzzah!
At attention, you dogs! It's time for your third trial!
Huh? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait a second!
No one said anything about a life-threatening challenge!
Life-threatening...
Dying is okay.
Don't worry about it, Liz, it's not gonna kill us, right?
Roara, rules!
Okay, so number one...
Balance the blocks while stacking them according to the color order on the instructions!
There are 5 levels, and you earn the same number of points as the level you clear.
Advancing to the next level is your call, but make a single mistake, and BOOM goes the bomb!
If you mess up the placement, and the bomb explodes...
...it's game over. So yeah, you lose, game over.
Alright, who's ready to get SMOKED?
Well, Gigi, do you wanna go first? Die.
I will take the first bomb!
I will die for Justice! For Justice!
Justice! For Justice!
Gigi, stand here! Look at you!
Wait, that's incredible!
10 seconds?
That's nine more than one!
That's standard math!
We can count to ten for you, okay?
Ten times one, guys!
Can you count to ten?
You at home, can you count to ten?
One! Two!
No, not yet! It's not time yet!
Okay, okay. Calm down, let's start.
Gigi, you ready?
I'm ready!
Three, two, one, go!
Oh, look at... it's blue and yellow...
I am the purple.
Okay, easy, easy! Good job!
You good?
How do you do that?
Did I scare you? Are you okay?
Yellow, green, go!
All of them!
Is that even possible?
Uh oh! Uh oh!
We always believed in you!
Go Gigi, go! Gigi, go!
This one you will have to do like a thingy at the...
She's doing it! White! Wow!
Now pose! Oh!
Hey, that's pretty good!
For ten seconds!
You gotta keep it! Keep it!
Six, five, four, three, two, one!
Yay! That was really good, Gigi!
Good job!
Oh, that's difficult!
Why'd the ghost do that?
This is not shade, this is praise!
It's really good.
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
One-one was a race horse, two-two was one too, one-one won one race, two-two won one too!
She got it! Wow!
Nice one, Gigi!
What?! Holy moly!
Why'd they put this one so far?
20 seconds is a long time.
You can do it! You can make it!
Can I?
What is this?
She's doing really well!
Go, Gigi, go!
Nine, eight, seven...
six, five, four, three, two...
One! Wow, four--
Ahhh!
For Justice!
Are you okay, Gigi?
Yay, she died! For Justice!
Gigi, are you okay?
Don't worry, she's just being mean to you. You're gonna be fine.
Ahhh! That's not fair!
That's not fair! I had to do math in two seconds! That's not fair!
Quick math, quicker!
You did amazing, though!
Died for Justice...
Gigi? Gigi, what are you doing?
Smells like a barbecue in here... You got 10 points!
Ten?!
I didn't even count that high!
Ten times one, that's ten!
Oh, who's next?
Someone else is gonna get blown up, right?
That's enough, chatterboxes! You're up, Raora.
I don't wanna get burned like Gigi!
She licked us! Gigi licked us!
So proud of you!
I'm ready to defuse the bomb!
You got this, Raora!
First, Level 1...
And in three, two, one, go!
Light blue, easy easy!
Purple, got this!
Tada! Tada!
Good job! Easy!
Oh, wow! That's a lot of colors!
Purple... green...
Three... green...
Yay!
I knew Smokey was nice!
Orange! Purple!
Okay, go, go, go! Do it!
You have a lot of time, don't worry.
Lots of time!
Go Raora, go!
Okay!
Pose! Pose! Pose!
Wait, this isn't fair, why?
Do you have to do a full-on...
Yeah, why not?
You just do the pose! Whatever pose you want!
What?! What?!
Okay! Huh?
I was trying to make her do those poses, huh? Huh?
Yeah, was that cute?
Ah yeah, very cute.
Oh, I'm in the way, I'm in the way.
It's fine, we can huddle.
Look at that, really good.
No! Wrong color! Wait, that's the wrong color.
Wrong color! She got this! She got this!
Oh, here we go.
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck,
if a woodchuck could chuck wood?
Yay!
Purple! Pink!
We don't need that when we're catching criminals!
Oh yeah, so many colors.
Okay, that's a lot of colors.
Yellow, yellow, black, blue! You're almost there!
Dark blue, dark blue! Wait, dark blue? Oh, it's fine.
Math!
35 plus 6 is 41!
Wow, she got that so quick! I'm so good at math!
Why are math questions on my shorter?!
Big cat, big brain! Good job, Raora!
Yay! She did it!
Pets for everyone! Pet pet pet pet...
Raora scored 15 points. Not bad for a blockhead.
15! Yay!
15! Good job, Raora!
Thanks! Yatta! Yatta!
Who's ready to get lit up next?!
Okay, I'm all fired up, I'm ready, I'm ready! Ow!
Stop fighting!
Okay, okay...
You know what, shut up! Keep it down, please.
Okay, thank you.
3, 2, 1, go!
Why is that a traffic cone?
Go CC, go! Go, go, go!
Whoa, it's so high! It looks like a candy.
That's hard to balance! It's hard to balance.
Go CC, go!
Okay, party cone! That's too many!
That's okay!
Purple, yellow... You got it! Yay, got it! Okay!
Yay!
Oh, that looks so yummy.
Yeah, this looks...
Green, yellow, red, light blue... I can't... I'm colorblind!
Green! You got it! Go, go, go!
Yay!
Oh, what's your pose? Pose on the left or on the right?
I'm so relaxed. Namaste.
10 seconds left! Now breathe in. Hold it! Hold it! Hold!
Hold... Breathe in...
Woo! All right!
Okay, red... Pink... Red, green...
Yellow... Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Wow, you're bringing over every single color!
The strategy, the strategy...
Balance, balance. Okay, you did it!
Okay, disarm the bomb with a tongue twister.
The big black bug bit the big black bear,
but the big black bear bit the big black bug back.
Yay! Look at your stuttering!
Speak!
Go! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, that was really fast!
Nice, nice! Guys, guys...
Yeah, white, white, blue... Winner!
What? Crumbling!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, you can do it!
Oh, that's black. Oh my god...
Oh my god, it's so over! Oh no!
Uh oh! Oh no, oh no! Colors, I'm colorblind!
I'm colorblind! I'm colorblind!
Ooh... Whoa!
You can't see me, right? Because I'm in the dark.
I love zombies.
Wait a second, did you look... did you look...?
Open your eyes! You've gotta face your fears!
Nice and smokey... 10 points!
I got 10! Woo!
And can you... can you count to...
can you count to...
10? How many fingers am I holding up?
At least four. At least...
At least four. Okay, well...
Queen! Leader of Justice... will take on this challenge!
For us, it's time...
Justice!
Show you what I'm made of!
Star!
All right. All right.
Okay. I didn't even get to the mark.
Oh, these blocks are quite far away.
All right. Let us watch...
Bring it on! Bring it on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Are you ready, Liz? We're going to count down for you, okay?
I'm ready!
All right. Level 1.
Three... two... one... Start!
Ooh, that's easy. Come on, come on, you got this.
Okay, she got this, she got this.
She got it.
Oh, the blue one is so far away!
She got it, she got it, she got it, she got it!
Uh-oh.
Okay, okay.
No, no, that one's good.
Oh, blue!
That one's there! That one's there!
All right. Yes!
Oh, that's... that's a pyramid.
Pyramid scheme! You got this!
I buy, tell, sell you, and then you sell it.
Wait, wait, wait! Go, go!
Put it there, put it there! You got this!
Woah, woah, woah!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!
Ooh! Yeah.
This pose does not seem fair.
Yeah, this pose... Any cool pose!
Ooh! Show us your coolest pose!
Oh, wow. Why did we get yoga, and they just get to do whatever they want?
Yeah! Yoga! They get photo shoots!
Oh gosh! Why are there so many?
She got this, she got this.
Nice pink! Got this.
Woah, fast! That's our queen!
That's our queen!
All right. Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair.
Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he?
What?!
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear! Fuzzy Wuzzy...
...was a bear! Fuzzy Wuzzy... I can't remember the rest!
Cats in boots and cats in boots and cats in boots...
Fuzzy Wuzzy here and there! Didn't see him anywhere!
Yeah, I'm the queen of Justice! And...
That's just... You know what rhymes with Justice! Think about it!
Just eyes!
Yeah! Just ice!
All right!
Okay, okay... Difficult!
The light one! And then I need the pink one and the blue one... Wait, no, I don't need this blue one!
Get out of here!
Light blue, light blue! You got it, you got it!
I need this one! I need this one! And I need...
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh!
No, no, no! Everything's falling apart!
No, stop! Don't fall apart!
Did I get it? No!
Out of my way!
Oh no!
What the freak?!
No!
You got it, you got it, that's fine.
I mean, yeah, that's fine. Well, whatever. It's...
Kick them! Kick them! Get out your anger, kick them!
I didn't want to do math anyway. It's fine.
I didn't want to do math anyway, it's fine, it's fine.
[Smokey: I got some math for you... 10 points!]
Did he blow us up, really?
10 points! Yay!
Whoo! Star!
I think that was pretty good. I think that was pretty good.
[Smokey: Simmer down, buttercups! You still got the final trial!]
Quizzes and tests?!
We don't want to do math anymore!
We just want to relax now. I'm getting tired.
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Let's go. I want ice cream now. Bye!
What... what the freak? Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey, I'm the only one still burnt up!
Hey, can I go... can I go shower real quick before the next... next game?
Huh? Hello?
Oh...
[Screen: Now Loading...]
Taking you up below, taking you all be... haha!
All right, I'm all showered up. I don't smell like a cheeky chicken... well, burnt cheeky chicken anymore!
Oh, maybe they're hiding. All right, I know a way to bring them out.
JUSTICE! JUST LIKE THAT!
JUST! THIS! GET! THAT!
Wait, wait, wait, you were hiding there the whole time? Oh goodness.
Hello, pretty kitty!
All right, up we get, up we get.
It's time for the final trial, twerps!
Cecilia, rules!
Okay! Yes, sir!
The final trial is... Hammer of Justice! Whack-a-Gnome!
Whack-a-Gnome! Gnome!
Okay, here are the rules. Number one:
Defeat the evil gnomes...
Evil?
...emerging from the wall by striking them with a giant hammer!
Number two! As we've all learned...
...not all gnomes are bad! Some are friendly, some are nice.
So be careful not to hit the good ones, and only hit the bad ones.
Only the bad ones, okay.
And then, if you smash the bad gnomes, you get 3 points.
And if you hit the good gnomes, you get minus 3 points.
Okay, so we're supposed to hit the bad ones.
How are we supposed to know? - We'll be able to tell.
Okay, okay. And then... be careful to aim carefully! And then at the end...
...how many points can you score in 30 seconds?
30 seconds!
So they come out of the holes, and then you have to hit them.
Good gnomes and bad gnomes.
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed to the worms!
Sunglasses inside!
And this is the good one. No friendly fire!
Red hat, no sunglasses, good. Green hat with sunglasses, don't hit!
Alright, put those muscles to work, big cat.
I got this one, guys! I got this!
There it is. Oh, come on, pretty kitty, it can't weigh that much.
I'm gonna ask Elizabeth to get me 5.
Believe in me who believes in thee! Let my voice be your strength! Pretty kitty, use your God eye!
Got this! I can do it!
Wait, wait, wait! I'm scared!
Ready to roll?
I have the power of justice and cute girls! I can do it!
All right, it's time to whack a gnome! Get ready!
Three! Two! One! Start!
30 seconds! Look at her going!
That's the power of justice right there! She's swinging fast!
Kill the gnome! Kill the gnome!
Oh god, the cucumber! Cucumber!
Oh gosh! Disgusting! Disgusting!
Why is there a cucumber?! What was that?!
Oh geez... What was that?
That was not a gnome! Ew...
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention hitting cucumbers gives you 5 points per hit.
What?! She hit it!
I feel like you should have said that earlier!
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game. Which one of you meatheads is next?! Move out!
Who's next? Liz, I think it's your turn now!
Oh, well, okay then. Let me just take off my jacket here, all right.
Flame off! Let's go!
All right, let me go get the hammer over here.
Time to earn your title, "leader"!
Are you ready, Liz?
I am ready.
Three, two, one, go! 30 seconds!
Crazy! She's going fast!
She's swinging it! Look at her go!
That's a lot of them! Get the bad ones!
Get the bad ones! Oh, the cucumber!
10 seconds, Liz! You got it!
Four, three, two, one! What the freak?!
I feel bad about hitting those gnomes. My granddad has gnomes in his garden.
You did amazing! They're usually quite nice.
Sympathy ain't gonna help you catch Advent! Gigi! Show no mercy.
Are you ready for this, Gigi?
Come over here and get the hammer over here.
That was heavy!
She's built for this. She does that every day.
I mean, it's not as heavy as the horn, so...
You can do this, Gigi! Go!
Come on, Gigi! Come on!
All right, just lift with your legs, lift with your legs!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Use your claws! With your legs!
Well done! Well done!
Gigi's strong today!
All right, Gigi! Break a leg, or break a gnome in this case!
All right, here we go! Three, two, one...
Start!
Oh, no! Gigi, Gigi!
Gigi didn't think that's how it worked! Oh...
No! That's the wrong color, Gigi! No!
Check the color! Check the color! Just the purple ones! Just the purple ones!
I got it! I got it! I got it!
Oh, well, she got the cucumber. Oh, yeah...
Yeah, yeah, maybe that evened out...
Eh? Eh? Eh? What?
Is it talking to her? I know what I must do.
I know what I must do!
Gigi, what are you doing? Why are you looking at me like this? Gigi?
No, Gigi! No, no, no! What are you doing? No, no, no!
Hey, someone just...
Why can't I hit her?! Oh, she's so good!
Why can't I hit her?! Oh...
Phew, I should learn that! That seems like a good dodge move.
Dodge! Dodge!
Hey, what's wrong with the camera...?
You must teach me that move sometime!
I will do it! When it jumps like that, it's crazy.
I don't know what happened, I just lost consciousness.
That cucumber, that was really impressive!
Thanks!
Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
[Smokey] Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
Okay, I'm ready! Avenge me!
Oh wait, I need the hammer.
Let's cheer for CC, okay?
Okay.
Here we go! It's time to whack a gnome!
All right! Three, two, one, go!
You know what, Smokey? You know what you are doing to us the entire time?
Yeah, you're trying to make us play games...
...but I'm not gonna play your games! I'm not gonna play...
...whack your gnomes, because I do not discriminate!
We're freeing all the gnomes!
You know what? I'm not discriminating!
She's gone hysterical!
She's gone hysterical! Um, all right...
Yeah! Go, go, go!
Die! You dirty...
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Sorry, sorry. I've had enough.
I've had enough, Smokey! You're pitting us against each other...
...but we will not play your games any longer!
We'll happily play your games...
No, it's just a joke, you know... Funny, you know.
We have humor too, not just strength, but...
...are you okay?
Goin' AWOL, huh!? 0 points, you slug!
[Smokey] Goin' AWOL, huh!? 0 points, you slug!
No way!
I don't want any more of you making us do sports the entire time! I'm sick of this!
It's okay, it's okay... Hey, hey...
Enough of you!
It's okay, I rock you...
Why do you keep bullying us, Smokey? Right?
La la la la...
I quieted somehow... Can we escalate this?
Wait, we need to stop this! Stop, hey, stop, stop, stop!
Hit me!
I'm sorry, Smokey...
We'll make sure that this is not gonna happen again... We're sorry! We're sorry!
Tell... Tell who had the highest score!
Just tell us... Tell us, Smokey! Come on, end this pain!
After four trials, one of you clowns came out on top...
[Smokey] After four trials, one of you clowns came out on top...
The winner is... Raora Panthera! You win, cupcake!
[Smokey] The winner is... Raora Panthera! You win, cupcake!
Yay! That's it! My pretty kitty!
Good job, good job, good job!
Good kitty, good kitty!
You're a good kitty, kitty, kitty... Good job!
Zip it! It's time for our winner to make her little announcement.
[Smokey] Zip it! It's time for our winner to make her little announcement.
A sweet little announcement!
We'll be performing the new song right now!
Right now?! Yeah!
Chatties, are you ready? Yeah!
It's gonna be so nice! We've been practicing...
...our singing and dancing really, really hard to perform for everyone today!
So make sure to watch our very first live performance...
...right now!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm
Infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll seek you out
Reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my veins, feel my pulse, it's rising and igniting
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
(Ah, ah)
Walking the line, fell so far into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Justice, it's just like that, I
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass
Is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out (Huh!)
The light goes out (Out!)
The light goes out
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly, never
Making a sound, incognito, light the pathway
Burning 'em out, in the fallout I'll stand in the ashes
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
(Ah, ah)
Walking the line, fell so far into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Justice, it's just like that, I
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass
Is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out (Huh!)
The light goes out (Out!)
The light goes out
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm
Infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
The light goes out
Yay!
Everyone, mina, what did you think of our performance?
Yeah! Make sure to stream Renegade! Let's get us to number one!
And also, guys, be sure to remember to share your thoughts, screenshots, and favorite moments from today's training...
...and live performance with the hashtag #Justice3D!
Yay!
Huh? What? No! I hate these alarms, it's so loud!
Is it an emergency? Let's take a look.
Oh, yes, you're right! You're right, Raora! All right, everyone, come over. Let's take a look.
Huh?
Advent!
They're dancing and singing!
Aw, they look so good! They look so adorable!
No, no, that can't be right!
Look, look! They're waving at us!
Yay!
They're on stage!
Do you think if we go to the stage we can catch them?
Mocchi! Mocchi!
We wanna go to the arena!
Do it! Yes! Yes!
[Smokey: All you punks think about is standin' on stage! Go, get out of my face! And make sure you catch Advent!]
We'll give them a taste of their own medicine, right, guys?
Yeah!
Justice! Just like that!
Justice! Let me do it!
Team, team, team! Go, go, go, get out of here!
Huzzah!
Where are they?
I've been here for five hours now.
Five hours!
Huzzah!
Six hours, maybe.
Gigi, we're here!
It took so long!
You look so great! You look so fun!
Well, I had to take a shower, you know.
Shower? Ah, cucumber, that's me, yeah.
Well, where are they?
They're gone!
They're gone?!
Maybe because you guys were too slow!
Gone!
Did you see them?
No.
Aha, I see how it is.
Well, you know... Silly.
Maybe we should perform the song we all worked so hard practicing.
Ooh, that sounds like a good idea!
Okay!
All right, let's get in positions, everyone!
In position! Okay, okay, okay!
One, two, three, four, let's go!
手を上げて
clap your hands 海の向こうまで
clap your hands 届きますように
Raise your hands
clap your hands beyond the sea
clap your hands so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に everybody
clap your hands 空の向こうまで
clap your hands 響きますように
Look, all together, everybody
clap your hands beyond the sky
clap your hands so that it resounds
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光差す 僕たちの未来
Our future, shining with light
4, 3, 2, 1
始めようか さぁ diving
Shall we begin? Now, diving
待っても意味ない timing
There's no point in waiting for timing
あの魚みたいに swimming swimming
Swimming, swimming like those fish
引き寄せるの lighting
Drawing in the lighting
まだ見えないよ maybe
Maybe we can't see it yet
この先には何があるのか？
What is waiting up ahead?
まだ早いよ take it
It's still too early, take it
追いつくまで shaking
Shaking until we catch up
でもたまに止まって thinking thinking
But stopping occasionally, thinking, thinking
変えてみせる change
I'll show you I can change
踏み出すのさ stepping
Stepping forward
掴んでみせるよ キラキラ my dream
I'll grab hold of my sparkling dream
叶う日まで story 繋ぐから
I'll connect the story until the day it comes true
だって君にずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me forever
手を上げて
clap your hands 海の向こうまで
clap your hands 届きますように
Raise your hands
clap your hands beyond the sea
clap your hands so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に everybody
clap your hands 空の向こうまで
clap your hands 響きますように
Look, all together, everybody
clap your hands beyond the sky
clap your hands so that it resounds
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
光差す 僕たちの未来
Our future, shining with light
今日はいらない ブレーキ
No need for brakes today
理性 壊せ breaking
Break your reason, breaking
何時でもいいでしょ？ 四六時中
Anytime is fine, right? 24/7
君は何を feeling?
What are you feeling?
解き放て sparking
Unleash the sparking
暗闇に放つ レーザービーム
A laser beam released into the darkness
光らせて stage 作るから
I'll light up and build this stage
だって君にもっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to watch me even more
手を上げて
clap your hands 海の向こうまで
clap your hands 届きますように
Raise your hands
clap your hands beyond the sea
clap your hands so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に everybody
clap your hands 空の向こうまで
clap your hands 響きますように
Look, all together, everybody
clap your hands beyond the sky
clap your hands so that it resounds
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
重なる wave 世界を 揺らせ
Overlapping wave, shake the world
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 do it!
終わりがある事 既に I know
I already know that everything must end
でも まだまだ 泳ぎ足りない の
But I still haven't had enough of swimming
give me crazy
まるで lazy?
Are you like lazy?
次元 混ざり合う の
Dimensions blending together
全て 塗り替える blue
Blue that repaints everything
手を上げて
clap your hands 海の向こうまで
clap your hands 届きますように
Raise your hands
clap your hands beyond the sea
clap your hands so that it reaches you
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands
ほら 一緒に everybody
clap your hands 空の向こうまで
clap your hands 響きますように
Look, all together, everybody
clap your hands beyond the sky
clap your hands so that it resounds
手を上げて
Raise your hands!
手を叩こう
Clap your hands!
光射す
Shining bright...
僕たちの未来
...our future!
Breaking Dimensions
Justice! Just like that! Justice! Yeah, yeah!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
Hit the fever, the moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door
Yeah!
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far
Always striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible
We're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
This is it!
Been smashing barriers left and right
That's our myth!
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
It's endless!
So get together, let's reunite!
Time to rise!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright
We've been together for what feels like an eternity
The times are changing, but we are ready for infinity
Yeah!
Our stories align
We're gonna go far when we combine
So look at the horizon and then look beyond
We'll marvel at the skies and the strength of our bond
We're making a vow to the smiling stars
A powerful moment that's all ours
The seasons change, but we keep shining
Now everybody sing!
Keep it going!
We're making our way to the next dimension
A million thrills in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention
Breaking tension, breaking through!
We won't miss!
With endless energy, stronger ties
We got this!
A perfect harmony we devise
We promise!
So clap along with me
Time to rise!
The future's right before our eyes
A new dimension of freedom that we've found
Yeah, we've made it
We're breaking out of the mold, no longer bound
We're unlimited
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo
No time to stop, we're good to go!
The whole wide world is listening
So everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension
There's no question, we'll break through!
Don't relent!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
It's advent!
It's awe-inspiring, going well
Represent!
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
Yeah!
That was... Amazing job today!
Congrats to all the trials that performed before us!
One more! What does it say?!
Justice! Justice! Just like that! Justice! Yeah, yeah!
But wait, not yet! We have not one, but TWO big announcements! Yeah!
First up, drumroll please...
Introducing the official Justice 3D Showcase Celebration Merch!
Alright everyone, get into your merch position!
Oh, merch position! Right! Okay!
Okay, first, we have... Sergeant Smokey Multi Case!
Where is it? Here! It's a multi case!
And if you also want to be Sergeant Smokey...
Now then, this is for you!
It's a handy item to store your favorite goodies.
On the left side, you can keep button badges and keychains.
The right side fits small acrylic stands and postcards!
Yay!
There's also a hook on the back to attach even more keychains!
We'd be so happy if you show off our merch at events, please!
Thank you so much!
Yay!
All right, Raora, your turn next.
My turn! Hmm...
All right, everyone!
Next up, next one is...
...the large size 3D Acrylic Stand!
Life-size! Life-size, baby!
Alas, Justice is not life-size...
I didn't even notice that! That's true!
I didn't notice until after I repeated it, and I was like, "Wait, life-size?"
Big cut means big acrylic!
Not that big, though! Big acrylic!
Large size!
In fact, Justice is coming to life as 3D acrylic stands!
Everyone loves acrylic stands, right?
Yeah! I love them!
So whether you have a room dedicated to acrylic stands or just starting your collection...
...you are going to need all of Justice, okay?
Get them all!
All of them! Yeah!
Liz, next one!
Oh, it's me! Haha!
Okay!
And as we all mentioned during our 3D showcases, we each have our own merch, too! Ooh la la!
All right then, I will start!
Hahaha!
This right here is the Paper Knife & Acrylic Stand!
It's a lovely set inspired by the design of my sword, Thorn! Yeah!
This paper knife can actually be displayed...
...by resting it on the acrylic stand!
It's so cool! You'll all get your own Thorn!
Yeah! Your baby Thorn! Baby Thorn!
So cute!
Oh gosh! I can't- I can't- Oh! It's so cool!
Gigi, your turn, your turn, your turn!
And now...
...a Hand In Cushion for Gramps!
Woo! Do you remember seeing it?
Sadly, there is no Ojisan to show you how soft and fluffy it is...
...but it is very fluffy, and it's made from a very squishy material!
You'll never want to stop squeezing it!
I'm going to squeeze it! Squeeze it, squeeze it!
And it's a Gramps!
Gigi!
Whoa!
CC! Check this out!
It's an Otomo Pouch & Socks set!
And if you want the socks, Monday, Tuesday, every day of the week, seven pairs of socks!
And then you have your little pouch, the little Otomo pouch to put it in, to store your...
...socks!
Yeah, it's really cute. You can put anything in it, of course, not only socks, but yeah.
I really like it. It's a little Otomo, and it reminds me of the Otomo pouch I made once.
I like it a lot! Please get it!
Okay, Raora! You could put your toes in your Otomo socks!
It's my turn!
And this is Raora's Pencil Case & Keychain set!
It's me wearing a Chatino costume, and...
...I'll be so happy if you fill it... It's so cute!
You like it? Yeah!
I'll be so happy if you fill it with...
...lots of stationery and use it at school or in the office or really anywhere you want!
And the keychain can be attached to the pencil case...
...so you clip it onto your bag or anything you like!
Super cute!
With soft sleeping Chatino.
Everything's really cute! I'm super excited to see you guys get them!
I'm very excited to see all of Justice's merch, and...
...if you want to know when can we purchase them...
...well, they will all be available to purchase right after this stream!
So make sure to check them out ASAP!
And that's our merch announcement!
That's... oh, the first one!
And as CC just mentioned, there is one more announcement!
And you all know, Justice will be performing live for...
...the very first time...
...at the hololive English 3rd Concert!
Woo!
Taking place at Radio City Music Hall in New York on August 23rd and 24th PDT!
And right after this stream...
...we will be redirecting you into the...
...music video of "ALL FOR ONE"!
Justice is also in there, of course, and maybe you'll see...
...maybe you'll see us doing some stuff! Who knows?
We'll be moving and grooving! Grooving baby!
So make sure to stay tuned! It's going to be very, very soon!
It's getting a little sad...
but it's almost time to say goodbye.
Before we go,
let's each share our thoughts and thank all our fans for their support.
Gigi, you go first.
Me? Me? Okay.
Grems! Thank you so much
for supporting us all this time!
And can you believe it's been a little over a year now?
And so many more years
with JustChats, Justice, and Grems!
Gosh... Hello...
Thank you so much!
Gosh, Rosarians, give me a mighty huzzah!
We did it!
Oh my gosh, thank you so much for joining all of us on our adventure here at Hololive!
I can't... I can't believe it! Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
And we're going to be in a concert!
And... everything's happening!
Like, all our dreams are coming true, and it's all thanks to you guys! Thank you so, so much!
Onwards!
And upwards!
Huzzah!
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much, everyone!
Thank you, JustChats, thank you, Otos, thank you, everyone!
Thank you, Justice, of course!
It's been a lot of fun.
We worked very hard, and I'm so excited and happy that you all got to see it finally!
And we're also really excited to be in the 3D concert, so, yeah!
Thank you from the bottom of our hearts
for supporting us thus far!
Please keep supporting us from now on!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Tutti, tutti, tutti, tutti, tutti, tutti!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice
for a whole year and many more to come!
This has been a dream come true for me,
being in 3D, dancing with you guys, and having fun!
So I really, really appreciate it.
Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart!
Big kiss!
We are Justice!
Once again, thank you all for watching our very first 3D collab stream today!
Please keep supporting Justice!
Justice!
Just like that!
Get get get that!
Bye-bye, everyone!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Make sure to eat, drink, hydrate, and all that jazz! All right, bye-bye!